(Penny:)Uh, no.
What do you do,
(Sheldon:)you just go out there
and gambol about
like a bunny?
(Penny:)No. I just run till I'm hungry,
then I stop for a bear claw.
(Sheldon:)Why are you doing that?
(Penny:)It's good to stretch your
muscles before you run.
(Sheldon:)All right.
All right,
(Penny:)let's start with a toe touch.
(Penny:)Okay, you do it.
I am doing it.
(Penny:)Oh. Wow. Good job.
(Penny:)Okay, um,
(Penny:)can you do this?
(Sheldon:)We'll never know.
(Penny:)Okay, let's just warm up
on the run.
(Leonard:)Okay.
Okay, let's go.
(Sheldon:)I've been reading up
on biomechanics.
(Sheldon:)I think you'll be
surprised at my...
(Penny:)Oh, my God,
are you okay?
(Sheldon:)I think so.
(Penny:)Oh, let me
help you up.
Thank you.